officelabs.com 2008-12-16

# Privacy Statement

_(last updated:  February 2008_) 

Microsoft is committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy statement applies to the data collected by Microsoft through the officelabs.com site (the "Site"); it does not apply to data collected through other online or offline Microsoft sites, products or services. 

**Collection of Your Personal Information**  
We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you or allows us to contact you. The personal information we collect may include your nickname. 

To sign in to the Site, you will be asked to enter an e-mail address and password, which we refer to as your Windows Live™ ID or your Microsoft Passport Network credentials. After you create your Windows Live ID, you can use the same credentials to sign into many different Microsoft sites and services, as well as those of select Microsoft partners, that display the Windows Live ID or Microsoft Passport Network logos. By signing in on one Microsoft site or service, you may be automatically signed in when you visit other Microsoft sites and services. To learn more about how your credential information is used when you sign into participating sites, please read the Microsoft Online Privacy Statement at [http://privacy.microsoft.com](http://privacy.microsoft.com/).

We may collect information about your visit, including the pages you view, the links you click and other actions taken in connection with the Site. We also collect certain standard information that your browser sends to every website you visit, such as your IP address, browser type and language, access times and referring Web site addresses. 

**Use of Your Personal Information**  
The personal information collected on this Site will be used to operate the Site and to provide the service(s) or carry out the transaction(s) you have requested or authorized. 

In support of these uses, Microsoft may use personal information to provide you with more effective customer service, to improve the Site and any related Microsoft products or services, and to make the Site easier to use by eliminating the need for you to repeatedly enter the same information or by customizing the Site to your particular preference or interests. 

Microsoft occasionally hires other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as Web site hosting. We will only provide those companies the personal information they need to deliver the service. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information and are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose. 

Microsoft may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Microsoft or the Site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Microsoft and our family of Web sites; or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Microsoft products or members of the public. 

Personal information collected on the Site may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Microsoft or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using the Site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. Microsoft abides by the safe harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union. 

**Control of Your Personal Information**  
Except as otherwise described in this statement, personal information you provide on the Site will not be shared outside of Microsoft and its controlled subsidiaries and affiliates without your permission. You can update information you provide on the Site, such as your nickname, through the Site. To learn more about how to control how we communicate with you, please read the Microsoft Online Privacy Statement at [http://privacy.microsoft.com](http://privacy.microsoft.com/).

Please be aware that this privacy statement and any choices you make on the Site will not necessarily apply to personal information you may have provided to Microsoft in the context of other, separately operated, Microsoft products or services. 

**Access to Your Personal Information**  
You can review and edit the personal information you provided at this Site by following the instructions on the Site. To learn more about how you can review and edit information in your Windows Live ID, please read the Microsoft Online Privacy Statement at [http://privacy.microsoft.com](http://privacy.microsoft.com/). 

**Security of Your Personal Information**  
Microsoft is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide on computer servers with limited access that are located in controlled facilities. Additionally, when we transmit sensitive personal information (such as a credit card number) over the Internet, we protect it through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol. 

**Use of Cookies**   
We use cookies on this Site to ensure the integrity of the registration process and to personalize the Site. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a Web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. 

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. For example, if you personalize a web page, or navigate within a site, a cookie helps the site to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of delivering relevant content, eases site navigation, and so on. When you return to the web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the site's features that you customized. 

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually [_modify your browser setting_](http://www.microsoft.com/info/cookies.htm) to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to use interactive features of this or other web sites that depend on cookies. 

**Use of Web Beacons  
** Microsoft Web pages may contain electronic images known as Web beacons - sometimes called single-pixel gifs - that may be used to assist in delivering cookies on our sites and allow us to count users who have visited those pages and to deliver co-branded services. We may include Web beacons in promotional e-mail messages or our newsletters in order to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon.

Microsoft may also employ Web beacons from third parties in order to help us compile aggregated statistics and determine the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns. We prohibit Web beacons on our sites from being used by third parties to collect or access your personal information.

 **Changes to this Privacy Statement**  
We may occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the "last updated" date at the top of the privacy statement. For material changes to this privacy statement, we will notify you either by placing a prominent notice on the home page of our web site or by directly sending you a notification. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy statement to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. Your continued use of the service constitutes your agreement to this privacy statement and any updates. 

**Contact Information**  
Microsoft welcomes your comments regarding this privacy statement. If you have questions about this statement or believe that we have not adhered to it, please contact us by clicking here: [mailto:olpfb@microsoft.com](mailto:olpfb@microsoft.com). 

Office Labs Privacy Feedback  
Microsoft Corporation  
One Microsoft Way  
Redmond, WA 98052-6399
